## LEELA MOHAN VENKATALA

#### **Senior Graphic Designer**

Hyderabad, Telangana mohanvenkatala@gmail.com +91 99598 99879

Hello! This is LEELAMOHAN VENKATALA

I am a Creative Graphic Designer, I Had 4yearsexperience, mostly I'm collaborate with digital marketing team and I made creative designs for 1. social media, 2. Video promotions, 3. website layout designs, 4. Broucher designs, and all kinds of print and web related designs.

mostly I'm worked in tough deadlines and under pressure.

I will make video slideshows, promotional videos and all branding design works.

I had "Freelance Graphic Design" Experience.

The Previous Companies I worked as a Graphic Designer are "MAYAPURI GRAPHIC WORKSTATION" "METROMEDI" (Freelancer)

"GTN INDUSTRIES LTD" For Freelance.

"Xenith Systems Pvt. Ltd." For Fulltime.

Please treat as a human being not as a slayer with your respectful behaviour.

Thank you for reading and looking my profile patiently.

#### Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1995-09-10 Eligible to work in: India

**Highest Career Level:** 2-5 years experience

**Industry:** Advertising, PR, MR, Event Management, Arts & Entertainment, Beauty & Wellness, Business Operations, Food Preparation & Service, Healthcare, IT Operations & Helpdesk, Marketing, Technology

Total years of experience: 4

## Work Experience

#### **Senior Graphic Designer**

Freyr global solutions pvt.ltd - Hyderabad, Telangana February 2022 to Present

#### **Graphic Designer**

Xenith systems pvt.ltd - Hyderabad, Telangana June 2019 to January 2022

## **Freelance Graphic Designer**

GTN INDUSTRIES LTD - Hyderabad, Telangana November 2019 to November 2020

## **Freelance Graphic Designer**

METRO MEDI - Hyderabad, Telangana April 2019 to October 2019

#### **Junior Graphic Designer**

Mayapuri graphic work station - Chennai, Tamil Nadu May 2018 to June 2019

#### Education

### PG DIPLOMA in multimedia technology in Graphic Design

 ${\it ICAT DESIGN AND MEDIA COLLEGE - Chennai, Tamil\ Nadu}\\$ 

June 2017 to March 2018

## Skills / IT Skills

- User Experience (UX)
- Adobe Photoshop (4 years)
- Adobe Illustrator (4 years)
- Adobe InDesign (4 years)
- Adobe Premiere (3 years)
- Adobe After Effects (3 years)
- Graphic Design
- Branding
- Illustration
- Typography
- Adobe Creative Suite
- User Interface (UI)
- Photography
- Adobe Acrobat
- · Wireframing
- Layout Design
- Logo Design
- Adobe Lightroom

#### Languages

- Telugu Fluent
- English Intermediate

- Tamil Beginner
- Hindi Beginner

# Online Profile

https://www.behance.net/mohanvenkatala1183